[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of Blofelds Swiss mountain refuge, which was destroyed in an air raid in the movie On Her Majestys Secret Service?", "correct_answer": "Piz Gloria", "incorrect_answers": ["Piz  Bernina", "Piz  Helvetica", "Piz  Sancta"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Once ground, how long does it take before coffee begins to stale?", "correct_answer": "Minutes", "incorrect_answers": ["Weeks", "Hours", "Months"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Fanta was named by a German salesman, named Joe Knipp. During a contest for employees, the contestants were told to let their fantasy run wild and Knipp said: Fanta.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what South American country was Che Ernesto Guevara born?", "correct_answer": "Argentina", "incorrect_answers": ["Paraguay", "Bolivia", "Suriname"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what 1967 movie did the pretty half of the duo announce as an introduction We rob banks?", "correct_answer": "Bonnie and Clyde", "incorrect_answers": ["Frankie and Johnny", "Harold and Maude", "Tango and Cash"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor starred as the character Che in the the 1996 movie Evita?", "correct_answer": "Antonio Banderas", "incorrect_answers": ["Benjamin Bratt", "Marc Anthony", "George Clooney"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the famous James Bond movie, what part of Dr. Nos body is prosthetic?", "correct_answer": "Hand", "incorrect_answers": ["Arm", "Foot", "Leg"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which band recorded a song called Brontosaurus which includes the following verse:\n\nNow her daddys getting old\nAnd he seemed to lose control\nWhen the brontosaurus\nStormed into the house to trap her.?", "correct_answer": "ELO", "incorrect_answers": ["Velvet Revolver", "Velvet Underground", "AFI"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Filipino word means money in English?", "correct_answer": "pera", "incorrect_answers": ["tindahan", "mura", "wala"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Samhainophobia is the fear of this holiday.", "correct_answer": "Halloween", "incorrect_answers": ["Valentines Day", "St. Patricks Day", "Christmas"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Most heroin-related deaths are not caused by an overdose but by a lethal combination with other drugs in the body.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "It was the largest rough diamond ever found, weighing in at 3 106 carats.", "correct_answer": "Cullinan", "incorrect_answers": ["Koh-i-Nor", "Malan", "Elizabeth"]}]